[Gus] Hey!
Pretty funny.
-Oh.
-Yes.
[Mickey imitates purring]
Fuck up.
I love this. What do you think?
I like it.
Be honest. When we first met,
did you think I was a bad dresser?
No, I didn't think you were
a bad dresser.
I just thought you hadn't bought
any new clothes since middle school.
[chuckling]
Well, you should talk.
When we first met, you were wearing
a swimsuit on dry land.
Uh, you loved my bathing suit, landlubber.
Yeah.
When we first met, no joke,
I thought you were Hungarian.
No.
I remember being surprised
that you spoke English.
-Are you serious?
-Kidding.
Oh, it's a joke.
But I do remember the first moment
I was, like, into you.
-Oh, really?
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, I wanna hear about this.
You were helping Bertie
carry her dresser into the house.
I saw your arms
and thought they looked sexy.
And I was like, "Yeah,
I'd fuck this guy if he was into it."
-What?
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God. I had no idea.
I should've made my first move.
And I thought you were so nice.
You were helping Bertie--
Okay, I don't need to hear that.
I get the nice thing enough.
Just objectify me. Please. I love it.
Sure.
So, stud, you gonna wear
this jacket tonight?
[smacks lips] I don't know.
Is it too cool?
I feel like I'm trying too hard.
That's my nightmare.
Your dumb movie title band
is playing a live gig.
This may never happen again.
You have to look good.
I know. It's just when I was shooting
my scene with Arya,
I was kind of a dick on set
with my friends, so I don't wanna roll up
wearing a new jacket and have
them be like, "Who's this asshole?"
I'm sure they're over it.
If not, fuck 'em.
Conflict is the cornerstone
of any good band,
like Metallica or the Spice Girls.
It's true.
[inhales] Okay, final verdict.
Do I buy this jacket?
Yes, you buy this jacket,
and I buy a pair of sunglasses
that I do not need. Hmm?
-All right.
-Yeah.
[theme music playing]
How about this? Too somber for you?
Way too somber.
I'm looking at that,
I wanna slit my wrists.
[chuckles] What do you want your suitcase
to say about you?
I want my luggage to say,
"Hey, Cruikshanks,
I'm an adult with luggage,
and I got my shit together."
And then it can just stop talking
after that.
Are you scared of your family?
No.
I mean, just not super stoked
about taking this trip.
Might have been nice if you had backup.
What?
It's nothing.
Just think it's a little weird.
No, I didn't hear you. What'd you say?
It's a little weird you didn't invite me
to meet your family.
We've been together for a while.
You met my dad.
Oh.
I'm sorry. I just...
I bought the ticket before you and me
were, you know, hot and heavy.
Plus, I don't even think
you'd want to go, Mickey.
It's going to be, like, five days.
And it's super, super boring.
It's like every boring thing
mushed together.
It's South Dakota and family
and church and relatives
and anniversary parties
and compact rental cars--
You don't have to pile it on.
It's not that big of a deal.
Would've been nice to be invited.
Maybe I'm crazy,
but I thought we were there.
Well, I think we are there. I just...
I want you to meet my parents
and my siblings.
You don't have to meet
all of my stupid cousins.
Heather's pretty cool, actually.
It's fine. You can drop it.
I'll meet them some other time.
Okay.
Hey, look at this. What? Hold on.
What's this car doing
in the luggage section?
Little weird?
[imitates honking]
Then it's like...
[imitates car beeping]
Doin' a little reverse.
-Sir?
-What?
-Can you not do that, please?
-Oh.
Sorry. I was just goofin',
trying to make my girlfriend laugh.
It's not working.
Yeah, I know.
Hey. Look at that.
Little fruit cart. Got mangoes.
-You love a mango.
-Yeah.
Yeah? Let me get you a mango. Okay.
Thank you. Thanks.
How is it? Good?
-It's delicious. Thank you.
-You're welcome.
[Gus] Ah!
There's an open house.
You wanna go check it out?
-Yeah, sure.
-Could be a little fun adventure.
[Mickey mutters]
[Gus] Okay. Yes.
Oh, hi, there. I'm Angela.
-Welcome.
-[Gus] Hello.
If you wouldn't mind, please put these on.
-They just redid the floors.
-Sure.
Before you look around, please sign in.
[Mickey] All right.
My name is Genevieve Vavance...
and I still have an AOL e-mail address.
You are Bastian. No last name.
Whoa.
Holy shit! Double sinks!
Oh, my God. I love it.
God, if we lived here... Oh, God,
we'd be living the high life, you know?
I'd set down my toothbrush, I'd be like,
"Mickey, why don't we invite
the Cunninghams over for dinner?"
Shit. Angela already hates us.
Okay, I'll do this.
There we go. Nobody will ever know.
Double sinks.
[Mickey] No, I'm addicted to my phone.
I'll text myself a reminder or something,
and then when my phone buzzes,
I get so excited
'cause I'm that desperate to text.
-I 100% get that.
-[exhales]
When you were telling the story
and you said your phone buzzed,
-I got excited.
-[chuckles]
Clearly, I'm still smoking.
It's just one too many things to quit
in a year.
And any negative thing you can say,
I've already thought.
Hey, no, don't worry about it.
You'll quit when you're ready. It's fine.
Yeah, I figured I've been smoking
since I was 15,
-what's a couple more months?
-Mm-hmm.
Yeah. And, hey, just so you know,
I'm here to talk about your sobriety
as much or as little as you want to, so...
Thank you.
There is one thing I could talk about.
Okay.
-So things are going really well.
-Mm-hmm.
And then, there was that whole
Dr. Greg meltdown,
and I went to this bar
with Truman and Stella
and I ordered a drink.
Oh, wow.
Now, before you get worried,
I did not drink it.
-Okay.
-But I really, really thought about it.
Your sobriety is the most important thing,
so I'm glad you didn't drink.
Yeah. Me, too.
[Gus] Uh-oh.
-[clicks tongue] Ugh!
-Somebody ain't happy.
Come on. She needs us here to make it seem
like this is some kind of hot property.
How much, uh, do you think
this place costs, anyway?
$1.2 million.
Wow.
You know, I could afford that
if I did every single thing differently
over the last 15 years.
Never say never. I believe in you.
Maybe one day
we could afford this place together.
Yeah.
I shouldn't have said that, should I?
-No.
-Did it freak you out?
No. No, no, no. I...
Honestly, I'm not opposed to... you know,
moving in sometime, together. Sometime.
Yeah. I've thought about it.
So neither of us are opposed.
-Let's get out of here.
-Okay.
Hey, I'm sorry I didn't ask you
to go to South Dakota.
I should have, and I'm sorry.
I want you to come.
-Don't worry.
-Would you come?
No. Don't worry. It's okay. We're past it.
No, I was being so stupid.
I was in my head with my family.
I truly want you to come.
Will you come? Please?
You don't have to invite me
'cause you feel bad.
-I'm not.
-Hmm. No, you were right.
I do want to meet your parents
and your siblings,
but not every Cruikshank in America.
And five days is a really long time.
Yeah. No. That makes sense.
-Yeah.
You ready for your big show tonight?
-Yeah, fuck yeah.
-[chuckles]
Actually, no. I don't think
we're ready to perform live.
-This shouldn't be happening.
-Oh.
Well, if it really starts to suck,
I can always just yell, "Fire,"
and take off my top.
-Perfect.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Hey, uh, you want a cigarette
before we go in?
Do you want me to have one?
Uh... Yeah, I'm just not really ready
to face Ruby and Wade yet.
They saw me go nuts on that shoot,
and our group-text chain
has pretty much gone silent.
[sighs] I've learned, if you own it
and you say you're sorry,
they usually forgive you.
Yeah. I mean, that makes sense.
You don't even have to mean it.
-No, I mean it.
-Oh, great. That'll help sell it.
I'll be there if you get nervous.
You can squeeze my hand.
-Okay.
-Yeah?
Yeah. Be prepared.
I'm gonna squeeze the shit out of it.
They're not gonna start
any trouble with me there.
Those guys are scared of me.
No. Yeah.
Hey, everybody.
[all] Hi.
Nice jacket.
-[Gus] Oh, thank you.
-All right.
You guys ready to shred?
-Oh, ready to shred. Ready to shred.
-Yeah.
Wait, guys. I just wanted to say,
as far as my tantrum on set
with Arya and stuff,
I feel really crummy--
Gus, I'm gonna stop you right there.
Come on, whatever happened on set,
let's leave it on set.
I feel like there was an apology coming.
I'd like to hear that.
-Okay.
-Mmm.
Uh, yeah, I mean, you guys
have helped me out so much,
and I know I lost my temper there
a couple of times,
so I am sorry.
Well, thank you.
I don't accept your apology.
Uh, my feelings are still hurting.
Seriously?
Not seriously, Mickey.
See, just kidding. Let's have a fun show.
[chuckles]
All right, I'll leave you rockers to it.
I'm not in this band. Bye.
-Okay. Bye.
-Let's go over the set list, huh?
-[Beth] Oh, yeah.
-[Gus] Yes, good idea.
Oh, hey, yeah. I do not think
that we should open with "Gran Torino."
I agree.
We should not start with a ballad.
We'll put the crowd to sleep.
I picked up a few more days
of extra work on Witchita.
That's great. I'm proud of you.
Yeah, they need me on set at seven a.m.,
so I can't go too crazy tonight.
God, listen to me. "On set."
Can you believe it?
No, I cannot.
Oh, shit. I'm sorry.
Can I get you a drink?
Oh, no, thanks. I'm not thirsty.
Are you sure?
I want to do more stuff for you.
Like buying you drinks
and buying you jewelry.
Don't buy me jewelry. Please.
Open a savings account.
Hey, buddy.
[chuckling] Hey! Hey.
-Hey, how's the Rand-man?
-Hey.
Hey, what's up?
-Are people calling me the Rand-man?
-I don't know. They should.
[both chuckle]
-You guys know each other.
-Yeah, we've met.
-Hi, Bertie.
-Hello.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
So, um,
when I was coming over here tonight,
I saw a big accident on the road.
Oh, no.
I think it was very serious.
There was two ambulances.
And, um, I thought there was
some kind of spaghetti involved,
but I think it had come
from inside the man on the motorcycle.
And, um...
Hey! What are you guys talking about?
Mickey! Could I ask you to join me outside
for a meeting of the Chamber of Champions?
Sure.
That's what I call our apartment.
It's just a fun thing I do.
I don't know why I do it.
Yes, I do. It's 'cause we're champions.
-Let's go.
-Okay. Bye.
-Uh, can I get you a drink?
-Oh, no, I'm good.
Oh.
I'll get you another one.
You can double fist it!
-Cool.
-[chuckles] Yeah, cool.
I'm sleeping with Chris.
What?
[sighs] We started hanging out.
First, it was just an emotional affair,
but then things took a turn,
and now it's a very physical affair.
And now I really like him.
What is it about our apartment
that turns us into philandering bad girls?
What should I do?
[smacks lips] Well,
I never told Gus about Dustin.
But if you have feelings for Chris,
maybe you should be honest with Randy
and cut things off.
[sighs] But he's so sensitive.
Last night, I came in and he was crying
to an episode of Storage Wars.
That's not a reason to stay with him.
Ugh. This situation is so fucked.
I'm fucked.
-You okay, buddy?
-Oh, yeah.
-You seem sort of...
-Yeah.
-Oh, sorry. [chuckles]
-...out of it or something.
It's okay if something's wrong.
-No, not at all. Yeah.
-Okay.
Uh, this will be fun tonight.
-Yeah. Yeah, I can't wait. Yeah.
-Yeah.
You excited about going back home?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, my parents' 40th anniversary.
You know that's going to be
a fucking wild party.
-[laughing]
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hats off to Mark and Vicki, man.
Those crazy kids.
Yeah. Let's hear it for those nutty kids.
-[chuckles] They stuck it out.
-Mm-hmm.
Hey, and Mickey's finally going to meet
the Cruikshanks, huh?
Yeah.
Well, uh...
No. I mean, she's not.
I invited her,
but she's not gonna come.
-Oh, bummer, man. Huh.
-Yeah.
I don't know. Maybe it's for the best.
I don't want her to see
how weird my family is.
Or how weird I am around my family.
It's gonna be a lot.
And Mickey's Mickey, right?
She could totally freak out
your whole family.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, you don't have to say that,
but yes.
It's maybe for the best.
-But I love her.
-Yeah.
-Oh, yeah, she's the best.
I'm just saying you could be, like,
playing Scrabble at your kitchen table,
and then she walks in,
bites the head off a bat.
[chuckles]
[hip hop music playing in background]
-Hey.
-Hi.
-Let me get you a drink.
-[chuckles]
Full disclosure, I'm here
with my boyfriend, and I don't drink.
Okay. Uh, well...
Which one's your boyfriend?
I gotta see if you're making a mistake.
Nice. Uh...
The guy in the military jacket.
[man] Seriously?
The dude who looks like a child's drawing?
Wow. You think you're funny, don't you?
We're done talking.
Oh, my God, it's almost show time!
-Oh, I can't wait.
-What the fuck is happening?
Did you just take my cigarettes?
-No.
-Yeah, you did. You're lying.
I'm not lying.
Why would I take your Kool Ultra Lights?
I'm not in seventh grade.
You're a really shitty liar.
If she said she didn't take 'em,
she didn't take 'em.
Dude, does this involve you?
Go back to your band,
which I heard sucks, by the way.
Uh, that's bullshit.
This is our first show,
so no one even knows we suck yet.
Prove you didn't take my cigarettes.
-Open your purse.
-Fuck you. No.
-Come on.
-Hey. Get the fuck out of here.
Relax.
No, I'm not going to relax.
Get fucking going, top button.
Whatever. Keep 'em.
I got better shit to do, anyway.
Then go do it!
I did take his cigarettes.
I figured.
Okay.
-See you in a little bit.
-Bye, buddy.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
We are Roger and The Eberts!
And we play theme songs
for movies that don't have them!
So let's start things off right,
with a little visit from the dessert cart.
One, two, three, four.
♪ I didn't come to Choco little ♪
♪ I didn't come to Choco little bit ♪
♪ I didn't come to Choco little bit more ♪
♪ I came to Chocolat ♪
♪ I didn't come to Choco little ♪
♪ I didn't come to Choco little bit ♪
♪ I didn't come to Choco little bit more ♪
♪ I came to Chocolat ♪
-[all clapping]
-[Mickey] Whoo!
Well, this next song is about a birdman,
and it's called "Birdman."
Three, four...
♪ Birdman! ♪
♪ Or the unexpected virtue of ignorance ♪
♪ Birdman, Birdman, Birdman, Birdman
Birdman, Birdman, Birdman ♪
[scattered applause]
♪ Footloose ♪
♪ This is the theme song for ♪
♪ This is the only song for ♪
♪ Footloose ♪
♪ God bless you, Sully ♪
♪ You saved my life ♪
♪ You saved my children ♪
♪ You saved my wife ♪
♪ God bless you, Sully ♪
♪ You saved my life ♪
♪ You saved my children ♪
♪ You saved my wife ♪
[cheering and clapping]
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
This last jam is dedicated to Mr. Eastwood
and my special girl,
Dobbsy.
One, two, three, four...
♪ Better than a grand piano ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Deeper than the Grand Canyon ♪
♪ You're my Gran... ♪
♪ Torino ♪
♪ And the skeleton says
Get off of my lawn! ♪
♪ That skeleton says
♪ Get off of my
Off of my lawn ♪
♪ Torino ♪
-♪ You're my Gran Torino ♪
-[all applauding]
-You guys fucking ruled.
-Oh... stop.
That was the best concert I've been to
in years, and I'm not even kidding.
Thanks, Mickey.
I want to go to South Dakota.
-Really?
-Yeah.
We're a team.
Let's go hang out in a fly-over state.
Oh. Should I not call it a fly-over state
in front of your parents?
-Probably best not to.
-Okay.
♪ 'Cause you know
We got to eat, eat, eat ♪
♪ You know we got to pray, pray, pray ♪
♪ So you know we got to love, love, love ♪
♪ Eat Pray Love, Love ♪
♪ You know we got to eat, eat, eat ♪
♪ Oh, you know
We got to pray, pray, pray ♪
We got to love, love, love ♪
♪ Eat, pray, love, love, love, love ♪
♪ Eat, pray, love, love
Eat, pray, love, love ♪
♪ Eat, pray, love ♪
♪ You know we got to pray, pray, pray ♪
♪ Oh, you know we got
To love, love, love ♪
♪ Eat, pray, love, love ♪
♪ You know I got to eat, eat, eat ♪
♪ Oh, you know
We got to pray, pray, pray ♪
♪ Well, you know
We got to love, love, love
♪ Eat, pray, love, love, love, love ♪
♪ Eat, pray, love, love ♪
♪ Eat, pray, love, love
Eat, pray, love, love ♪
-♪ Eat, pray, love ♪
-[audience cheering]
[Gus] Thanks a lot.